export const quiz10 = [
  {
    question: "What does a programmer do?",
    answers: [
      "design and develop software by using algorithms and data structures in a programming language",
      "create programming languages",
      "create problems that can only be solved using software",
      "makes sure that IT systems are running and are up to date in an organization",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What can be used as a data type in programming?",
    answers: ["all the rest", "numbers", "letters", "words"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is an algorithm?",
    answers: [
      "An algorithm is a step-by-step process that defines a set of instructions",
      "An algorithm is an educated guess of what a system will return as an output",
      "An algorithm is a list of to-dos that a programmer needs to accomplish at work",
      "An algorithm is a recipe on how to create an application",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Select an example of two popular programming languages?",
    answers: [
      "Python and Java",
      "Silver and Crast",
      "A-Star and D--",
      "TTCC and Marvel",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Name the two basic instructions used in programming?",
    answers: [
      "If Clause and Loops",
      "SQL and Query",
      "Classes and Graphs",
      "Compiler and interpreter",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the objective of programming?",
    answers: [
      "To solve problems, automate tasks, and create new products using by creating software programs",
      "To create problems in existing processes and products",
      "To create programming languages for every person to speak to a machine",
      "To solve problems by creating a program for every issue in the world",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is a programming language?",
    answers: [
      "Programming languages are a set of rules that determine how to write instructions that a computer can understand",
      "Are languages that are spoken by machines so they can talk to each other",
      "Programming languages are a set of keywords used by programmers to collaborate between them to solve a problem",
      "Are languages that only programmers can understand and use at the workplace to communicate more efficiently",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "How can a computer understand the instructions written by a programmer?",
    answers: [
      "Through instructions written in a programming language which are converted into a machine-readable format through the process of compilation or interpretation",
      "Through diagrams and schemas drawn by programmers on a piece of paper that they upload to the computer",
      "Through instructions written in multiple programming languages which are machine-readable after multiple processes of compiling, translating, and interpreting",
      "Through requests written in a programming language that they put directly on the hardware",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What are the main two most basic concepts used in programming?",
    answers: [
      "Algorithms and data structures",
      "Classes and objects",
      "APIs and HTTPS requests",
      "Big Data and Machine Learning",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "How can businesses use programming to develop and distribute digital content?",
    answers: [
      "All the rest",
      "By creating channels and automated processes to distribute content",
      "By creating digital art that can be used and enjoyed by end-users",
      "By creating applications that are used by people to interact with",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What does a programmer do?",
    answers: [
      "design and develop software by using algorithms and data structures in a programming language",
      "create programming languages",
      "create problems that can only be solved using software",
      "makes sure that IT systems are running and are up to date in an organization",
    ],
    answer:
      "design and develop software by using algorithms and data structures in a programming language",
  },
  {
    question: "What can be used as a data type in programming?",
    answers: ["all the rest", "numbers", "letters", "words"],
    answer: "all the rest",
  },
  {
    question: "What is an algorithm?",
    answers: [
      "An algorithm is a step-by-step process that defines a set of instructions",
      "An algorithm is an educated guess of what a system will return as an output",
      "An algorithm is a list of to-dos that a programmer needs to accomplish at work",
      "An algorithm is a recipe on how to create an application",
    ],
    answer:
      "An algorithm is a step-by-step process that defines a set of instructions",
  },
  {
    question: "Select an example of two popular programming languages?",
    answers: [
      "Python and Java",
      "Silver and Crast",
      "A-Star and D--",
      "TTCC and Marvel",
    ],
    answer: "Python and Java",
  },
  {
    question: "Name the two basic instructions used in programming?",
    answers: [
      "If Clause and Loops",
      "SQL and Query",
      "Classes and Graphs",
      "Compiler and interpreter",
    ],
    answer: "If Clause and Loops",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the objective of programming?",
    answers: [
      "To solve problems, automate tasks and create new products using by creating software programs",
      "To create problems in existing processes and products",
      "To create programming languages for every person to speak to a machine",
      "To solve problems by creating a program for every issue in the world",
    ],
    answer:
      "To solve problems, automate tasks and create new products using by creating software programs",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a programming language?",
    answers: [
      "Programming languages are a set of rules that determine how to write instructions that a computer can understand",
      "Are languages that are spoken by machines so they can talk to each other",
      "Programming languages are a set of keywords used by programmers to collaborate between them to solve a problem",
      "Are languages that only programmers can understand and use at the workplace to communicate more efficiently",
    ],
    answer:
      "Programming languages are a set of rules that determine how to write instructions that a computer can understand",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How can a computer understand the instructions written by a programmer?",
    answers: [
      "Through instructions written in a programming language which are converted into a machine-readable format through the process of compilation or interpretation",
      "Through diagrams and schemas drawn by programmers on a piece of paper that they upload to the computer",
      "Through instructions written in multiple programming languages which are machine-readable after multiple processes of compiling, translating and interpreting",
      "Through requests written in a programming language that they put directly on the hardware",
    ],
    answer:
      "Through instructions written in a programming language which are converted into a machine-readable format through the process of compilation or interpretation",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the main two most basic concepts used in programming?",
    answers: [
      "algorithms and data structures",
      "classes and objects",
      "APIs and HTTPS requests",
      "Big Data and Machine Learning",
    ],
    answer: "algorithms and data structures",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How can businesses use programming to develop and distribute digital content?",
    answers: [
      "All the rest",
      "By creating channels and automated processes to distribute content",
      "By creating digital art that can be used and enjoyed by end users",
      "By creating applications that are used by people to interact with",
    ],
    answer: "All the rest",
  },
  {
    question: "What role does backend development play?",
    answers: [
      "To create the server-side logic of a web app",
      "To design the web app",
      "To create the content of the web app",
      "To create the user experience of the web app",
    ],
    answer: "To create the server-side logic of a web app",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a content management system?",
    answers: [
      "An app used to create, manage, and modify content for a website",
      "A programming language",
      "A web framework",
      "A tool deploy websites",
    ],
    answer: "An app used to create, manage, and modify content for a website",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the database used for?",
    answers: [
      "Store data that is used for the website",
      "Create the website",
      "Store websites",
      "Create data for the website",
    ],
    answer: "Store data that is used for the website",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a web framework?",
    answers: [
      "A collection of tools and libraries used to create a website",
      "A tool to design websites",
      "A user interface",
      "A type of web server",
    ],
    answer: "A collection of tools and libraries used to create a website",
  },
  {
    question: "What defines a responsive design?",
    answers: [
      "All the rest",
      "A design that applies for all types of devices",
      "A design that applies for different screen sizes",
      "A design that works well with both dark theme and light theme",
    ],
    answer: "A design that applies for different screen sizes",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is NOT a core technology of web development?",
    answers: ["Mobile development", "CSS", "HTML", "JavaScript"],
    answer: "Mobile development",
  },
  {
    question: "What role does frontend development play?",
    answers: [
      "To create the visual interface including the interactions for a website",
      "To manage the content of the website",
      "To create the user experience of a website",
      "To distribute web application in multiple languages",
    ],
    answer:
      "To create the visual interface including the interactions for a website",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a content management system?",
    answers: [
      "None of the answers",
      "A framework created to build web apps",
      "A programming language to create websites",
      "A tool used to create content for a website",
    ],
    answer: "None of the answers",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a domain name?",
    answers: [
      "An unique name that identifies a website on the internet",
      "A name used for a web server",
      "A name used to identify a web page",
      "An address used to find a website",
    ],
    answer: "An unique name that identifies a website on the internet",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a web hosting service?",
    answers: [
      "All the rest",
      "A service that provides a domain name for a website",
      "A service that provides a web server for a website",
      "A service that provides storage space for web pages",
    ],
    answer: "A service that provides a web server for a website",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the ability of machines to perform tasks that would normally require human intelligence?",
    answers: [
      "Artificial intelligence",
      "Data science",
      "Data learning",
      "Machine intelligence",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the field of AI that focuses on developing algorithms to extract information from images and videos?",
    answers: [
      "Computer vision",
      "Natural language processing",
      "Video translation",
      "None of the answers",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the most important thing to keep in mind when developing and deploying AI systems?",
    answers: [
      "All the answers",
      "AI systems should be aligned with human values",
      "AI systems need to be transparent and accountable",
      "AI systems should be made to be fair and unbiased",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the most important thing that we need to do to ensure that AI is accessible to everyone?",
    answers: [
      "All the answers",
      "Invest in education and training to ensure that everyone has the skills and knowledge to use AI",
      "Promote the responsible development and use of AI",
      "Develop affordable and accessible AI tools and resources",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the future of AI?",
    answers: [
      "All the answers",
      "AI will be used to replace humans for manual tasks",
      "AI will be used to solve challenges that humans cant",
      "AI will become a big part of our lives",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is artificial intelligence (AI)?",
    answers: [
      "All the rest",
      "The ability of machines to mimic human behavior.",
      "The ability of machines to think and learn like humans.",
      "The ability of machines to perform tasks that would normally require human input.",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the field of AI that focuses on developing algorithms to understand and generate natural language?",
    answers: [
      "Natural language processing (NLP)",
      "Speech recognition",
      "Computer vision",
      "None of the answers",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What type of AI algorithm can be used for ads?",
    answers: [
      "Recommendation engine",
      "Guess engine",
      "Ads learning",
      "Tracking engine",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a potential benefit of AI?",
    answers: [
      "Making certain jobs not needed anymore",
      "Increasing productivity",
      "Creating new products and services",
      "Improving decision making",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is NOT a way to measure the success of an AI system?",
    answers: ["Social impact", "Recall", "Accuracy", "Precision"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a type of supervised learning?",
    answers: [
      "Regression",
      "Unsupervised learning",
      "Dimensionality reduction",
      "Reinforcement learning",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following occurs when a model learns the training data too well and is unable to generalize to new data?",
    answers: ["Overfitting", "Guessing", "Underfitting", "Overestimating"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the input for a machine learning model?",
    answers: ["Data", "Parameters", "Commands", "Code"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of a machine learning model?",
    answers: ["Prediction", "Estimation", "Data", "Variables"],
  },
  {
    question: "What type of machine learning model is given labeled data?",
    answers: [
      "Supervised learning",
      "Deep learning",
      "Unsupervised learning",
      "Reinforcement learning",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is a field of study that gives computers the ability to learn without being explicitly programmed?",
    answers: [
      "Machine learning",
      "Database programming",
      "Data mining",
      "Web programming",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of a machine learning algorithm?",
    answers: ["A model", "A hypothesis", "An educated guess", "A feature"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which type of machine learning does not receive labeled data?",
    answers: [
      "Unsupervised learning",
      "Semi-supervised learning",
      "Reinforcement learning",
      "Supervised learning",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is a parameter that is set before the training of a machine learning model?",
    answers: ["Hyperparameter", "Label", "Feature", "Instance"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is a set of data used to tune the hyperparameters of a machine learning model?",
    answers: [
      "Validation set",
      "Training set",
      "Development set",
      "Testing set",
    ],
  },
];
